[
    {
        "option1": "I must shall be a doctor.",
        "option2": "I have to a doctor.",
        "option3": "I have to be a doctor.",
        "option4": "I must have to be doctor.",
        "question": "আমায় ডাক্তার হতেই হবে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I can did be a doctor.",
        "option2": "I could be a doctor.",
        "option3": "I should be a doctor.",
        "option4": "I could a doctor.",
        "question": "আমি ডাক্তার হতে পারতাম",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "The good boy plays football well.",
        "option2": "The well boy plays football good.",
        "option3": "The good boy plays football good.",
        "option4": "The well boy plays football well.",
        "question": "ভালো ছেলেটি ভালো ফুটবল খেলে",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Her time was good tomorrow.",
        "option2": "Her time was well yesterday.",
        "option3": "She had a well time tomorrow.",
        "option4": "She had a good time yesterday.",
        "question": "কাল ওর ভালো সময় ছিল",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "He looks not well.",
        "option2": "He is not looking well.",
        "option3": "He has not looked good.",
        "option4": "He is looking not good.",
        "question": "তাকে ভালো দেখাচ্ছে না",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Mathematics can do very well.",
        "option2": "I can Mathematics very good.",
        "option3": "I can do Mathematics very well.",
        "option4": "Mathematics can very good.",
        "question": "অঙ্ক বেশ ভালো পারি",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "My son loves me very.",
        "option2": "My son loves to me very much.",
        "option3": "My son very loves me.",
        "option4": "My son loves me very much.",
        "question": "আমার ছেলে আমায় খুব ভালোবাসে",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "My son loves me very much.",
        "option2": "My son loves very very to me.",
        "option3": "My son very loves to me .",
        "option4": "My son loves me very very much.",
        "question": " আমার ছেলে আমায় খুব খুব ভালোবাসে",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "He drinks much water in a day.",
        "option2": "He drinks many water in a day.",
        "option3": "He drinks a lot of water in a day.",
        "option4": "He drinks more water in a day.",
        "question": "সে দিনে অনেক জল খায়",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "There is no many water in the pond.",
        "option2": "There is not much water in the pond.",
        "option3": "There is no lot of water in the pond.",
        "option4": "There is not more water in the pond.",
        "question": "পুকুরটায় বেশী জল নেই",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I thank you very much.",
        "option2": "I thank to you a lot.",
        "option3": "I thank very much you.",
        "option4": "I thank a lot to you.",
        "question": "তোমায় অনেক ধন্যবাদ",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "But there are much frogs in the pond.",
        "option2": "But more frogs have there in the pond.",
        "option3": "But lot of frogs have in the pond.",
        "option4": "But there are many frogs in the pond.",
        "question": "পুকুরে কিন্তু অনেক ব্যাঙ আছে",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Potato is no a fruit.",
        "option2": "Potato is no any fruit.",
        "option3": "Potato is not a fruit.",
        "option4": "Potato is not fruit.",
        "question": "আলু কোনো ফল নয়",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]